seedsheets.com 2018-03-12

# Privacy Policy — Seedsheet

**Last revised on June 28, 2017.**

This notice describes Cloudfarm Inc.’s (“We”, “Us” “Our” or “Cloudfarm”) Privacy Policy. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we will attempt to do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we use that information, and the choices we offer, including how to access and update information.  By visiting www.seedsheets.com (the “Site”), you are expressly accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of this Site, please review our Terms of Use.

 **TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED**

 **Information You Give Us**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give us in any other way. You provide information to us when you register, sign in, manage your accounts, search for a page or product, place a product order, return an item, send us an e-mail, comments or other material, participate in a survey, contest, questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and telephone number; gender; size; credit card information; e-mail address; or contact information of people to whom purchases have been shipped (for example, a gift recipient). If you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products or access certain services, offers and content on our Site. When you share information publicly, whether with us or others, it may be indexable by search engines.

 **Information Automatically Collected**

We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Like many websites, we use “cookies” that may uniquely identify your browser or account, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Site or other content served by or on behalf of our Site on other websites. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, browser language, version and time zone setting, hardware settings, browser plug-in types and versions; operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features or promotions; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, or from our Site, including date and time, cookie number, search queries, the phone number from which you called us, SMS routing information, and your favorite stores. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Website for fraud prevention and other purposes. We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches. During some customer visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes. Finally, we may use electronic image requests (also called “web beacons” or “single-pixel gifs”) to count page views and to access cookies. The web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personal information; rather they are used to compile anonymous information about Site usage.

 **Mobile**

When you use a location-enabled device to interact with our services, we may collect and process information about your location and your mobile device, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device or a unique identifier for your device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers. Most mobile devices allow you to disable location services; these controls are typically located in the device’s settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device’s location services, we recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.

 **What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide customized features such as storage of items in your “Cart” between visits to the Site. We may use information collected through devices and technologies such as “cookies,” pixel tags, or anonymous identifiers when you interact with the Site or the Site’s features that may appear on other websites. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted from your device at the end of a session.

 **Can I Avoid Cookies?**

You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of seedsheets.com features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Cart or proceed to Checkout, you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently, and you may not be able to use certain features on the Site.

 **How We Respond to “Do Not Track” Signals**

“Do Not Track” is a privacy preference that internet users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on the Do Not Track option, the browser sends a message to websites requesting them not to track the user. At this time, we do not respond to Do Not Track browser settings or signals. For information about Do Not Track, visit www.allaboutdnt.org.

 **Information from Other Sources**

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. For example, we may receive updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties which we use to correct our records.

 **Use of Your Information**

By visiting our Site, you agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to enhance our marketing and promotional efforts, to trace and analyze Site usage, to improve our Site content, appearance, utility, and product offerings, to offer you tailored content, to respond to your requests, or to customize our Site content, layout, and services. You agree that we may use your information, such as your e-mail address, to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as administrative notices, product offerings, participation in market research, special discounts or promotions, the and communications relevant to your business with Cloudfarm.

 **Do We Disclose the Information It Receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business. We are not in the business of selling any personally identifiable information about you to others. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

 **Product Manufacturers and Affiliate Partners**

We may operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with other manufacturers or affiliate partners and may share our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with these manufacturers or affiliate partners when necessary, for example, to complete or ship your order to the correct address.

 **Third-Party Service Providers**

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing or cleaning data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. Such third parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for other purposes. In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

Third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

 **Security**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

 **Links**

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

 **Children’s Privacy**

CLOUDFARM DOES NOT SELL PRODUCTS FOR PURCHASE BY CHILDREN.  We sell products only for purchase by adults. We do not direct our Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of eighteen.  

YOU MUST BE 18 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER TO SUBMIT PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US, INCLUDING TO REGISTER. YOU MUST BE 18 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER TO PLACE AN ORDER ON THE SITE OR PARTICIPATE IN ONE OF OUR ONLINE PROMOTIONS,  

We also ask that minors under the age of 18 NOT submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor (under the age of 18), you can use our Site only in conjunction with your parent’s or guardian’s permission.  If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information online, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us at info@seedsheets.com.

 **Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, websites, subsidiaries, or business units, or be acquired by another company. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, but usually remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless the customer consents otherwise). We reserve the right to transfer customer information in our possession as part of any such transaction.

 **Legal Disclosure to Protect Cloudfarm or Others**

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with any law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including investigation of potential violations; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Cloudfarm, our users, or others as required or permitted by law. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud detection, security or technical issues, or credit risk reduction. We may disclose information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we believe necessary to comply with an investigation of illegal activity. In addition, it may be necessary to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute.

 **Aggregated Information**

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with others such as publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

 **International**

We process personal information on our servers, which are currently located in the United States, but in the future may also be located in other countries. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

 **What Choices Do You Have?**

You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other features on the Site. You can add or update certain information. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those set out in this Privacy Policy.

At all times, you have the option of “opting out” of receiving future email marketing updates by sending to us an email with “unsubscribe” in the subject line at info@seedsheets.com.  Even if you opt out, you may continue to receive non-marketing email messages from us, including, for example, order confirmations.

 **Terms of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit seedsheets.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice and our Terms of Use including limitations on damages, disputes, and choice of law. If you have any concern about privacy at seedsheets.com, please email info@seedsheets.com with a thorough description of your concern, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use may change also. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. Please note that we will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

 **Notice to California Residents**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84 give you the right to ask us for a notice describing the categories of Personal Information we share with third parties or among our affiliated companies, for their direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year.  If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please send an email message to info@seedsheets.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and body of your message.  Please allow 30 days for a response.

 **Questions And Contact Information**

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@seedsheets.com.
